When you decided to do Parking Lot Pimpin', was it the first idea?
No.
So where did it land in the process?
Its purpose was to build audience that cared about the things that I cared about.
What I wanted to do is really present myself as this fire-ass poet who's really doing things in a different way,
giving the Beyonce-esque visuals and getting features on albums.
I've done one.
Like in the three years, I've done one feature on an album, which I'm really grateful for.
What was the album?
Earth Gang's album, Ghetto Gods.
Do you know who else has a spoken word feature on an album?
Do you?
On a Pitbull album.
Wow.
Before he became like Mr. 305, when he was like rapper Pitbull.
Like I have a whole poem on a Pitbull album.
I'm going to have to go back.
I mean, I had a spoken word time.
I had a whole era of spoken word.
And I commend all of y'all who have kept it going because it really felt like, okay, we're done with this.
And then it's like, no.
And that was really one of my goals.
I felt like it had been pushed to the side and even being here in the city of Atlanta, what the scene was.
Like dissipated.